[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Farmer Teds nickname in the movie Sixteen Candles?", "correct_answer": "The Geek", "incorrect_answers": ["The Spaz", "The Dork", "The Nerd"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do we call the study of male health and male diseases?", "correct_answer": "andrology", "incorrect_answers": ["ophiology", "oology", "Testrology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The character Rebecca Donaldson on the TV show Full House was meant to be a love interest for Danny Tanner but because of her popularity she became Jesse Katsopolis love interest.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did Troy travel to see Gabriella in High School Musical 3?", "correct_answer": "by truck", "incorrect_answers": ["by boat", "by train", "by plane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The mother determines the sex of the baby.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor played Buford T. Justice, the sheriff who was in hot pursuit of the Bandit in the 1977 film Smokey and the Bandit?", "correct_answer": "Jackie Gleason", "incorrect_answers": ["Paul Newman", "Tom Skerritt", "Dom DeLouise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fruit of this deciduous shrub or small tree is a berry 5 - 12 cm (2 \u2013 4.7 inches) in diameter, with thick red skin and about 600 seeds.", "correct_answer": "Pomegranate", "incorrect_answers": ["Pear", "Persimmon", "Pawpaw"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A cat that was trapped in one of the burning rooms in The Towering Inferno was rescued by security guard played by  O.J. Simpson.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the movie Sixteen Candles come out in the movie theatres in the United States?", "correct_answer": "1984", "incorrect_answers": ["1982", "1983", "1985"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word refers to leotard-like undergarment that has snaps at the crotch?", "correct_answer": "Bodysuit", "incorrect_answers": ["Camisole", "Bloomers", "Brassiere"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A chalazion, also known as a Meibomian gland lipogranuloma, refers to which of these?", "correct_answer": "A cyst on the eyelid", "incorrect_answers": ["A fungal rash", "A recurring headache", "A sore throat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How are mermaids portrayed in the collection of stories Arabian Nights, or One Thousand and One Nights?", "correct_answer": "As identical to humans", "incorrect_answers": ["As having a fish body and a human head", "As having a fish tail", "As having serpent bodies"]}]